好了  开始吧
Okay, here we go.
这只不过是个冰棒而已嘛
Okay, this is just frozen mustard.
但是是从哪里进口的
But from where?
是在法国制作的黄色第戎雪糕
A light yellow dijon originally crafted in France
但是加工地在肯塔基州
but now manufactured in Kentucky...
浸泡加工了一次
Dipped once...
不对
no.
是两次
Twice!
浸泡在热狗味的水里
In hot dog water.
啊
Ah.
太激动人心了
Inspiring.
獠牙来了  獠牙来了
Fangs is here! Fangs is here.
噢  是那本书里的女孩么
Ooh, the girl from the book?
对  你们猜准了
Yeah. You guys were right.
我意识到如果我要获得主演资格的话  就必须放手一搏
I've realized that if I want this part I have to do something really big,
所以我聘请了獠牙来引导我演出真正的狼性
so I hired fangs to help me tap into my inner wolf.
丽芙·鲁尼  你的快递
Delivery for Liv Rooney?
- 在这里签收  - 好的
- Sign here. - Okay.
哦
Oh.
这是什么  是不是獠牙把她的行李都提前运过来了
That's so weird. Maybe fangs had all her bags shipped here?
这是獠牙吗
Is that fangs?
不对  哥们  这是另外一个给狼养大的姑娘吧
No, munch, it's a different girl who was raised by wolves.
獠牙你好啊
Hello, fangs!
我是丽芙啊
Me Liv!
我在她的书里学到这招的
I read this in her book.
她必须要熟悉一下陌生人的气味
She has to get used to the smell of new people.
你的气味我能接受
Your scent is acceptable.
抱歉运来了个笼子
Sorry about the cage.
我的狼性太强了  我怕我在陌生人面前控制不住自己
My wolf instincts are strong, and I don't trust myself around new humans.
再说了  把我当货物运更便宜
Plus, it's cheaper to travel in cargo.
那好  獠牙  这是我的弟弟们
Well, fangs, these are my brothers.
不骗你  我还真习惯了
Not gonna lie, I'm into this.
很高兴你的来电  鲁尼
Glad you called, Rooney.
我不会错过任何一个能保证狼
I never miss a chance to make sure wolves
在传媒上大放光彩的机会
are accurately portrayed in the media.
那好吧  如果别人问到了  我就会很骄傲的说
Well, then, if anyone asks, I will proudly state for the record
你没有吃我的奶奶或是把房子炸了什么的
that you did not eat my grandma or blow my house down.
看见了吧  刚才那叫
See, that right there?
无礼攻击
Offensive.
我们开始吧
Let's begin.
特里斯坦·莱肯是狼人  半身是狼
Tristan Lycanth is half-wolf.
狼是庄严而又凶猛的生物
Wolves are majestic, fierce creatures.
你身上有这些特性吗  鲁尼
You got any wolf in you, Rooney?
呃  不  她没有
Um, no. No, she does not.
丽芙  她闻过了我的胳肢窝
Liv she sniffed my pits.
我可不敢忽悠她
I can't lie to her.
嚎叫一声听听
Howl for me.
这是成为一只狼最重要的部分
It's the most important part about being a wolf.
这宣示了你的尊严
It asserts your dominance.
我的嚎叫声是有尊严又花哨的
Well, my howl is dom-alicious.
鲁尼  我们的工作量不小啊
Rooney, we have work to do.
什么
What?
你要学会向狼一样生活  捕猎  进食
You're gonna live like a wolf, hunt like a wolf, eat like a wolf
甚至要向狼一样大便
and poop like a wolf.
噢  我可以给她演示最后一种
Oh, I can show her the last one.
没错  我可以模仿 84 种动物大便的方式
Yeah, I can imitate the pooping styles of 84 different animal species.
非常感谢你提供的便便样本  小子
Your offer of a poop demo is appreciated, little man.
但是丽芙现在是我的学生了
But Liv's my student now.
欢迎进入狼的生活
Welcome to my wolf pack.
这简直太酷了
This is gonna be so awesome.